https://meditateinireland.com/privacy-policy/

Comments
By using this website, you consent to the collection, processing and use of data as described below. This website can be visited without registration. This data such as pages called or name of the retrieved file, date and time are stored on the server for statistical purposes, without this data are directly related to your person. Personal data, in particular name, address or e-mail address are collected as far as possible on a voluntary basis. Without your consent, the data will not be passed on to third parties.
In cooperation with our hosting providers, we endeavor to protect the databases as far as possible against unauthorized access, loss, misuse or counterfeiting.
We point out that the data transmission in the Internet (eg in the communication by E-Mail) can exhibit security gaps. A complete protection of the data from access by third parties is not possible.
By using this website, you consent to the collection, processing and use of data as described below. This website can be visited without registration. This data such as pages called or name of the retrieved file, date and time are stored on the server for statistical purposes, without this data are directly related to your person. Personal data, in particular name, address or e-mail address are collected as far as possible on a voluntary basis. Without your consent, the data will not be passed on to third parties.
Processing of Personal Data
Personal data is any information that relates to a specific or identifiable person. An affected person is a person through whom personal information is processed. Editing includes all dealings with personal information, regardless of the means and procedures used, including, but not limited to, storing, posting, obtaining, deleting, storing, modifying, destroying, and using personal data.
We process personal information for the duration necessary for the purpose or purposes. For longer-term storage obligations due to legal and other obligations to which we are subject, we restrict the processing accordingly.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Newsletter Data
If you would like to receive the newsletter offered on this website, we need an e-mail address from you, as well as information that allows us to verify that you are the owner of the specified e-mail address and that you agree to receive the newsletter , Further data is not collected. We use this data exclusively for the delivery of the requested information and do not pass it on to third parties.
You can revoke your consent to the storage of data, the e-mail address and its use for sending the newsletter at any time, for example via the “unsubscribe” link in the newsletter.
Google Adwords
This website uses Google Conversion Tracking. If you have reached our website via an advertisement sent by Google, Google Adwords will set a cookie on your computer. The conversion tracking cookie is set when a user clicks on a Google-served ad. These cookies lose their validity after 30 days and are not used for personal identification. If the user visits certain pages on our website and the cookie has not expired yet, we and Google may recognize that the user clicked on the ad and was redirected to this page. Each Google AdWords customer receives a different cookie. Cookies can not be tracked through the websites of advertisers. The information gathered using the conversion cookie is used to Conversion statistics for AdWords advertisers who have opted for conversion tracking. Customers are told the total number of users who clicked on their ad and were redirected to a conversion tracking tag page. However, they do not receive any information that personally identifies users.
If you do not want to participate in the tracking, you can refuse the required setting of a cookie – for example, via a browser setting that generally disables the automatic setting of cookies or sets your browser to block cookies from the domain “googleleadservices.com”.
Please note that you are not allowed to delete opt-out cookies as long as you do not want to record measurement data. If you have deleted all your cookies in the browser, you must set the respective opt-out cookie again.
Sign up to our Newsletter
Get the Latest News & Events
Classes
Tradition
Calendar
Menu
Classes
Tradition
DISCONNECT TO RE-CONNECT!
© 2020. Tara Kadampa Meditation Centre. # CHY 11413. Website by Upala Design.
